it's on the ruler
moleque
yesterday I went to Feitosa
yesterday our
it was at the pet shop
pet shop
seven days to go
and today the Charlie Brown guys are going to invade the downtown area
we go on this
cheating on the coast
Uncle Charlie Brown
we are going to Praia Grande
we have
lucky we have too
one way another you can believe they come
it's connected to it
O what you are
looking like that guy you saw that guy who does
what does he do now
makes a paranoia
the contact we wanted
talking to the woman was doing the nail bro
now we have to see the other place
that we programmed
sorry for the delay
I spoke with the person in charge
said that
won't be able to give you due attention
because of this
warm contact right
so we lost two trips
speaks brother
so we're a little far away
took a while
it's us
bye bye Valeu
valeu
my life is like a Spike movie
true
complicated
moody and violent
understood
I started with the Brother freezer
good is
I agree with real
ha ha ha
I'll dig whatever you want
just can't be mané
vagabond heart the
people are at thirteen points in the city of Santos
do like this
I'm telling you a good one and let me
I do this part here
let us do marketing
I confirm with you
and then we send four hundred
it's energy
to believe in the brand drew
this one is more important to me bag
we are negotiating face
if you give good my brother
it's a blast
will give
make a sale
people burst
can tell them
that stop that we were exchanging ideas
will speak now
wait
i doubt an hour that i've done this
that we will do bro